[
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f8643e1c2c26c86b270aae8"
    },
    "question": "What is the first line of the FBLA creed",
    "correctChoice": "I believe education is the right of every person",
    "choices": [
      "I believe education is the right of every person",
      "FBLA is founded on honor, respect, and high achievement.",
      "I believe competition is the right of every person",
      "FBLA is founded on serving our community through our achievements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f88db5aae4c318e1c470aaa"
    },
    "question": "What kind of attire is acceptable for FBLA activities?",
    "correctChoice": "Business Attire"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f88db9dae4c318e1c470aab"
    },
    "question": "Does the FBLA primarily support March Of Dimes as a charitable organization?",
    "correctChoice": true
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f88dbf6ae4c318e1c470aac"
    },
    "question": "How many FBLA administrative regions are there?",
    "correctChoice": "5",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "7",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f88dc3bae4c318e1c470aad"
    },
    "question": "What parliamentary procedures(off which book) do FBLA meetings follow?",
    "correctChoice": "Robert's Rules",
    "choices": [
      "Robert's Rules",
      "Jack's Rules",
      "Mark's Rules",
      "Henry's Rules"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f88dc92ae4c318e1c470aae"
    },
    "question": "What is the outline written every Auguset detailing the state chapter's tasks and goals?",
    "correctChoice": "Program of Work"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f88dcbeae4c318e1c470aaf"
    },
    "question": "13 People currently serve on the NJ FBLA Executive Board.",
    "correctChoice": false
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f88dd48ae4c318e1c470ab0"
    },
    "question": "Where was the FBLA-PBL state office located until 1967?",
    "correctChoice": "Montclair State College",
    "choices": [
      "Duke University",
      "Montclair State College",
      "Wichita State University",
      "In Hamden L. Forkner's basement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "5f88ddedae4c318e1c470ab1"
    },
    "question": "The concept of FBLA was developed at what university?",
    "correctChoice": "Columbia University",
    "choices": [
      "Rider College",
      "Montclair State College",
      "Columbia University",
      "UW Lacrosse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82554ae9a9d618c7b3b"
    },
    "question": "Where was the FBLA-PBL state office located until 1967?",
    "choices": [
      "Carnegie Mellon University",
      "Montclair State College",
      "Duke University",
      "Dordt College"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Montclair State College"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b3c"
    },
    "question": "Where was the FBLA-PBL state office located at from 1967 to 1994?",
    "choices": [
      "Wisconsin-Stout University",
      "The local courthouse",
      "Beloit College",
      "Rider College"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Rider College"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b3d"
    },
    "question": "The concept of FBLA was developed at Stanford.",
    "correctChoice": false
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b3e"
    },
    "question": "FBLA started out as a _________ organization.",
    "correctChoice": "collegiate"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b3f"
    },
    "question": "What were the first four kinds of FBLA membership?",
    "choices": [
      "Active, Associate, Collegiate, and Honorary",
      "Active, Unactive, Collegiate, and Junior",
      "Low, Medium, High, Very High",
      "Temporary, Active, Collegiate, and Honorary"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Active, Associate, Collegiate, and Honorary"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b40"
    },
    "question": "When was the first FBLA NLC event held?",
    "choices": [
      "June 1964",
      "May 1952",
      "March 1950",
      "December 1987"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "May 1952"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b41"
    },
    "question": "The first fBLA NLC event was held at Conrad Hilton Hotel in Chicago.",
    "correctChoice": true
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b42"
    },
    "question": "Who founded the Alumni Division?",
    "correctChoice": "James Price"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b43"
    },
    "question": "When was the Alumni Division founded?",
    "choices": [
      "1967",
      "1971",
      "1975",
      "1979"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "1979"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b44"
    },
    "question": "When did the Fall Virtual Business Finance Challenge begin?",
    "choices": [
      "January 13",
      "October 21",
      "December 14",
      "June 8"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "October 21"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b45"
    },
    "question": "Regional Competitive Events are held on December 8-12.",
    "correctChoice": false
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b46"
    },
    "question": "What date of the year is American Enterprise Day?",
    "correctChoice": "November 15"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b47"
    },
    "question": "November is known as what month?",
    "choices": [
      "Cancer Awareness Month",
      "American Heart Month",
      "Prematurity Awareness Month",
      "National Kidney Month"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Prematurity Awareness Month"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b48"
    },
    "question": "When is the March of Dimes World Prematurity Day?",
    "choices": [
      "November 10",
      "November 11",
      "November 13",
      "November 17"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "November 17"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b49"
    },
    "question": "National Community Service Day is February 15th",
    "correctChoice": true
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b4a"
    },
    "question": "What month is February known as?",
    "correctChoice": "National Career and Technical Education Month"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b4b"
    },
    "question": "Who is the current FBLA-PBL National President & CEO?",
    "choices": [
      "Alexander Graham",
      "Sam Kessler",
      "Kelly Scholl",
      "Aric Mills"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Alexander Graham"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b4c"
    },
    "question": "Who developed the concept of FBLA?",
    "choices": [
      "Ashlee Woodson",
      "Hamden Forkner",
      "Gayle Robinson",
      "Eric Jones"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Hamden Forkner"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b4d"
    },
    "question": "A local chapter with 99 members would be entitled to 5 National Leadership Conference voting delegates?",
    "correctChoice": false
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b4e"
    },
    "question": "What are the FBLA colors?",
    "correctChoice": "Blue and Gold"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b4f"
    },
    "question": "In what month is FBLA week",
    "choices": [
      "February",
      "April",
      "March",
      "May"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "February"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b50"
    },
    "question": "What are the three words on the FBLA emblem?",
    "choices": [
      "Service, Education, and Leadership",
      "Service, Education, and Progress",
      "Service, Leadership, and Prosperity",
      "Progress, Leadership, and Education"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Service, Education, and Leadership"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b51"
    },
    "question": "The three categries of competitive events are: individual, team, and chapter.",
    "correctChoice": true
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b52"
    },
    "question": "What is the official FBLA website?",
    "correctChoice": "www.fbla-pbl.org"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b53"
    },
    "question": "Which of the following is not an official publication of FBLA-PBL",
    "choices": [
      "Tomorrow's Business Leader",
      "Business Leaders of Tomorrow",
      "FBLA Adviser's Hotline",
      "The PBL Business Leader"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Business Leaders of Tomorrow"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b54"
    },
    "question": "Where was the first FBLA local chapter organized",
    "choices": [
      "Knoxville, TN",
      "Cedar Rapids, IA",
      "Miami, FL",
      "Johnson City, TN"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Johnson City, TN"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b55"
    },
    "question": "The Georgia FBLA State Rally is held each year in Macon, GA",
    "correctChoice": false
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b56"
    },
    "question": "When must dues be received to qualify for competitive events?",
    "choices": [
      "April 1",
      "April 15",
      "March 1",
      "March 15"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "March 1"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b57"
    },
    "question": "FBLA involves nearly how many members?",
    "choices": [
      "250,000",
      "200,000",
      "350,000",
      "180,000"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "250,000"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b58"
    },
    "question": "The first FBLA State Chapter was in Iowa.",
    "correctChoice": true
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b59"
    },
    "question": "The FBLA-PBL National Center is located where?",
    "correctChoice": "Reston, VA"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b5a"
    },
    "question": "When was the FBLA Middle Level Division established?",
    "choices": [
      "1991",
      "1994",
      "1993",
      "1992"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "1994"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b5b"
    },
    "question": "How many goals does FBLA-PBL have?",
    "choices": [
      "11",
      "7",
      "9",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "9"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b5c"
    },
    "question": "What is the fiscal year of FBLA-PBL",
    "correctChoice": "July 1 - June 30"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b5d"
    },
    "question": "Joining a student organization will not help promote leadership development",
    "correctChoice": false
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b5e"
    },
    "question": "What does CTSO stand for?",
    "choices": [
      "Career & Technical Student Organizations",
      "Consumer & Technical Student Organizations",
      "Computer & Training Student Organizations",
      "Crossfit & Training Student Organizations"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Career & Technical Student Organizations"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b5f"
    },
    "question": "What is the color of candle that represents the chapter?",
    "choices": [
      "blue",
      "red",
      "orange",
      "white"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "white"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b60"
    },
    "question": "Dr. Edward Millar was the first executive director of FBLA-PBL",
    "correctChoice": true
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b61"
    },
    "question": "Who is the Conference Director of FBLA-PBL?",
    "correctChoice": "Richard Bowen"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b62"
    },
    "question": "Who is the Director of Membership for FBLA-PBL",
    "choices": [
      "Lisa Smothers",
      "John Harris",
      "Mark Smith",
      "Conrad Hilton"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Lisa Smothers"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b63"
    },
    "question": "Who is the Director of Education for FBLA-PBL",
    "choices": [
      "Han Harry",
      "John Keith",
      "Barbara Small",
      "Kennedy Jacks"
    ],
    "correctChoice": "Barbara Small"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b64"
    },
    "question": "What animal is on the FBLA emblem?",
    "correctChoice": "Eagle"
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "603ac82954ae9a9d618c7b65"
    },
    "question": "FBlA-PBL is mostly funded through swag sales.",
    "correctChoice": false
  }
]
